youthink.com 2003-06-22

# YouThink.com - Privacy Policy

|    
YouThink.com Online Privacy Policy 

YouThink.com takes great pride in utilizing state-of-the-art security procedures. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web site. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. 

This policy will let you know: 

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you and how it is used;   
2\. Who is collecting your information and with whom may your information be shared;   
3\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information;   
4\. How YouThink.com protects your personal information;   
5\. How you can access, update or delete your information;   
6\. What cookies are and how they are used; and   
7\. What else you should know about your online privacy.   

1\. What personal information does YouThink.com collect from you and how is it used? 

YouThink.com may collect information in several ways from different parts of our Web site. Some personal information may be gathered when you register. During registration, YouThink.com asks you to create a user ID and password, email (optional) and certain other personal information. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. In addition to registration, we may ask you for personal information at other times, including, but not limited to, (a) when you enter a prize giveaway, test, sweepstakes, contest or promotion sponsored by YouThink.com and/or our many partners, or (b) should the occasion arise, if and when you make a purchase using YouThink.com. If you contact YouThink.com, we may keep a record of that correspondence. YouThink.com also occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for internal research. Wherever YouThink.com collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.   
YouThink.com`s primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a customized experience on our Web site. This includes personalized services, interactive communications, possibly even online shopping, and many other types of services. In order to provide services free of charge, we display advertisements. By knowing a little about you, YouThink.com is able to deliver more relevant advertisements, content and better service to you. 

YouThink.com does internal research on our users-- demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration, during a promotion, or from our server log files. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. 

2\. Who is collecting your information and with whom may your information be shared? 

Information recorded during your use of YouThink.com is kept strictly confidential to YouThink.com. As a general rule, YouThink.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Its sole use is to facilitate your use of YouThink.com’s Website. For example, some YouThink.com services may be offered in conjunction with a partner company. In order to provide this co-branded service to you, it may be necessary for us to share your personal information with our partner company. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than YouThink.com, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service. 

Promotions that run on YouThink.com may be sponsored by companies other than YouThink.com or may be co-sponsored by YouThink.com and another company. Some or all of the data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion, if you don’t want your data to be shared. 

If you make a purchase from a store which may be hosted by YouThink.com or another merchant, the information obtained during your visit to those stores, and the information you give such as your credit card number and contact information, is provided to the merchants. This is to enable transactions to take place. 

Under confidentiality agreements, YouThink.com may match user information with third party data. Also, YouThink.com discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, % of our users are female) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. Please be aware that YouThink.com advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Web sites linked to YouThink.com are not covered by this privacy statement. 

YouThink.com may also disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) YouThink.com=s rights or property, other YouThink.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. YouThink.com may also disclose user information that we deem necessary to maintain and improve our products and services. 

3\. What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information? 

If you indicated upon registration that you are interested in receiving offers or information from YouThink.com and our partners, we may occasionally send you e-mail about our products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only YouThink.com (or agents working on behalf of YouThink.com and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. YouThink.com does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service or not to participate in certain promotions or contests. 

4\. How does YouThink.com protect my personal information? 

Keeping your personal information private is very important to us. Knowing that you use certain services or features may help us to offer you better and more relevant content, services and advertisements. But as with all personally identifiable information, we do not make this available to any third parties without your permission. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user. Please note that there may be several places on the YouThink.com Web site where you can transmit credit card information in order to complete a purchase transaction or for verification purposes. Any time we ask for a credit card number we transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, YouThink.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

5\. What is YouThink.com's policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information? 

You may edit any personal information entered with YouThink.com at any time by using your YouThink.com [password]. If you have forgotten your password, it can be retrieved by clicking the forgot password link. 

6\. What are cookies and how does YouThink.com use them? 

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, YouThink.com uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer=s hard drive. All sites on YouThink.com where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. 

Cookies are used by YouThink.com to (a) remind us of who you are and to access your account information in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service; (b) assist merchants to track visits to and business at their stores, and to process the items purchased by you; and (c) measure certain traffic patterns, which areas of YouThink.com’s Web site you have visited, and your visiting patterns in the aggregate. This cookie is set when you register or `Sign In` and is modified when you `Sign Out` of our services. This information collected by cookies is sometimes called `clickstream` or `click trail` and may also describe which pages you have seen in each merchant’s store. We use this research to understand how our users= habits are similar or different from one another so that we can make each new experience on YouThink.com a better one. We may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will see on our sites. You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those YouThink.com services that require registration in order to participate. 

7\. What else should I know about my privacy? 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you=re online. You should be aware that when you are on YouThink.com`s Web site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other Web sites from YouThink.com and all of its subsites that take you outside our service. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement or a YouThink.com search result, the click takes you off the YouThink.com Web site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that may use YouThink.com=s logos as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online - for example, via message boards or chat - that information can be collected and used by people you don=t know. While YouThink.com strives to protect its users= personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk. 

Your Acceptance to These Terms 

By using this Web site, you signify your assent to the YouThink.com online privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Web sites. Your continued use of the YouThink.com Web sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept these changes. 

Additional Information. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to YouThink.com. 

Policies for Individuals Under 13 YouThink.com encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites. No information should be posted or submitted to YouThink.com`s Web site by guests under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. 

Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, YouThink.com does not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. No information collected from guests under 13 years of age is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside YouThink.com. 

All registrants receive e-mail confirming their registration. In addition, when a guest under 13 registers, his/her parent or guardian receives an e-mail communicating that registration as well as instructions on how the parent or guardian could delete the registration if so desired. 

Although guests under 13 years of age may be allowed to participate in contests, if such a guest wins, notification and prizes are sent to the parents or guardians identified in the initial registration process. 

Guests` e-mail addresses are only posted on YouThink.com’s Web site with the consent of the member. 

Policies for Individuals 13 Years of Age or Older 

With the permission of a guest who is 13 years of age or over, information submitted at the time of registration may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by YouThink.com and may be shared with our business partners or companies that have been prescreened by YouThink.com. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use -- either by e-mail request or by modifying his/her registration information online. Once you have registered with YouThink.com, every effort will be made to maintain your information in a secure environment by YouThink.com. 

**youthink.com** uses WebTrends Live to analyze traffic to this web site. WebTrends Live does not create individual profiles for visitors. Unlike some tracking services WebTrends Live does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. WebTrends Live only collects aggregate data. For more information about WebTrends Live privacy policy, please click [**here**](http://www.webtrendslive.com/privacy_policy.htm).   

|
